<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<examples>
    <example>
        <witness>The black cat</witness>
        <witness>The black and white cat</witness>
        <witness>The black and green cat</witness>
        <witness>The black very special cat</witness>
        <witness>The black not very special cat</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>The black dog chases a red cat.</witness>
        <witness>A red cat chases the black dog.</witness>
        <witness>A red cat chases the yellow dog</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the black cat and the black mat</witness>
        <witness>the black dog and the black mat</witness>
        <witness>the black dog and the black mat</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the black cat on the table</witness>
        <witness>the black saw the black cat on the table</witness>
        <witness>the black saw the black cat on the table</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the black cat sat on the mat</witness>
        <witness>the cat sat on the black mat</witness>
        <witness>the cat sat on the black mat</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the black cat</witness>
        <witness>THE BLACK CAT</witness>
        <witness>The black cat</witness>
        <witness>The, black cat</witness>
    </example>
<!--    <example>
        <witness>the white and black cat</witness>
        <witness>The black cat</witness>
        <witness>the black and white cat</witness>
        <witness>the black and green cat</witness>
    </example> -->
    <example>
        <witness>a cat or dog</witness>
        <witness>a cat and dog and</witness>
        <witness>a cat and dog and</witness>
    </example>
     <example>
        <witness>He was agast, so</witness>
        <witness>He was agast</witness>
        <witness>So he was agast</witness>
        <witness>He was so agast</witness>
        <witness>He was agast and feerd</witness>
        <witness>So was he agast</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the big bug had a big head</witness>
        <witness>the bug big had a big head</witness>
        <witness>the bug had a small head</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the big bug had a big head</witness>
        <witness>the bug had a small head</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the bug big had a big head</witness>
        <witness>the bug had a small head</witness>
        <witness>the bug had a small head</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the drought of march hath perced to the root and is this the right</witness>
        <witness>the first march of drought pierced to the root and this is the </witness>
        <witness>the first march of drought hath perced to the root</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the drought of march hath perced to the root</witness>
        <witness>the march of the drought hath perced to the root</witness>
        <witness>the march of drought hath perced to the root</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>the very first march of drought hath</witness>
        <witness>the drought of march hath</witness>
        <witness>the drought of march hath</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>When April with his showers sweet with fruit The drought of March has pierced unto the root</witness>
        <witness>When showers sweet with April fruit The March of drought has pierced to the root</witness>
        <witness>When showers sweet with April fruit The drought of March has pierced the rood</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde wedded newe a wyf</witness>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde wedded a newe wyf</witness>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde newe wedded a wyf</witness>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde wedded newly a wyf</witness>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde E wedded newe a wyf</witness>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde newli wedded a wyf</witness>
        <witness>This Carpenter hadde wedded a wyf</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>Almost every aspect of what scholarly editors do may be changed</witness>
        <witness>Hardly any aspect of what stupid editors do in the privacy of their own home may be changed again and again</witness>
        <witness>very many aspects of what scholarly editors do in the livingrooms of their own home may not be changed</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>Du kennst von Alters her meine Art, mich anzubauen, irgend mir an einem vertraulichen Orte ein Hüttchen aufzuschlagen, und da mit aller Einschränkung zu herbergen.</witness>
        <witness>Du kennst von Altersher meine Art, mich anzubauen, mir irgend an einem vertraulichen Ort ein Hüttchen aufzuschlagen, und da mit aller Einschränkung zu herbergen.</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>Auch hier hab ich wieder ein Plätzchen</witness>
        <witness>Ich hab auch hier wieder ein Pläzchen</witness>
        <witness>Ich hab auch hier wieder ein Pläzchen</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>ταυτα ειπων ο ιϲ̅ εξηλθεν ϲυν τοιϲ μαθηταιϲ αυτου περαν του χειμαρρου των κεδρων οπου ην κηποϲ ειϲ ον ειϲηλθεν αυτοϲ και οι μαθηται αυτου</witness>
        <witness>ταυτα ειπων ― ιϲ̅ εξηλθεν ϲυν τοιϲ μαθηταιϲ αυτου περαν του χειμαρρου των κεδρων οπου ην κηποϲ ειϲ ον ειϲηλθεν αυτοϲ και οι μαθηται αυτου</witness>
        <witness>ταυτα ειπων ο ιη̅ϲ εξηλθεν ϲυν τοιϲ μαθηταιϲ αυτου περαν του χειμαρρου του κεδρου οπου ην κηποϲ ειϲ ον ειϲηλθεν αυτοϲ και οι μαθηται αυτου</witness>
    </example>
    <example>
        <witness>I bought this glass, because it matches those dinner plates.</witness>
        <witness>I bought those glasses.</witness>
    </example>  
</examples>
