<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

    CollateX - a Java library for collating textual sources,
    for example, to produce an apparatus.

    Copyright (C) 2010 ESF COST Action "Interedition".

    This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.

    This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.

    You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
    along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

-->

<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">
	<properties>
		<title>How to contribute</title>
		<author email="ndrscotti@yahoo.com">Andrea Scotti</author>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<section name="Access to launchpad.net">

			<p>To carry out the following instructions you have to have installed Bazaar: http://bazaar.canonical.com/en/.</p>

			<p>
				At first make sure you have an account on "Lanchpad" ; if not request one at Ronald Dekker (Ronald.Dekker@huygensinstituut.knaw.nl) that will guide you to the registration area . Then go to
				lanchpad => www. launchpad.net
			</p>

			<p>If you still have not used Launchpad you need to generate an SSH public key. This means you have to use the command line "ssh-keygen" on your pc as follows:</p>

			<pre>$ ssh-keygen</pre>

			<p>
				Once you´ve done that just copy and paste the key in the SSH box of your home page in launchpad. Make sure has been uploaded.
			</p>

			<p>Be sure you have commited to Bizarre the modification you have carried out on the file/s in collateX. To get the list of the modified file/s you have to write on the command line: bzr status.
				This will show the transformed files. You can avoid to commit some files of your collatex working dir by using the command "bzr ignore namefile". When done just write: bzr commit -m. You can add a
				comment after the command line to explain what you´re committing by using single upper commas before and after the text.</p>

			<p>At this point Bizaar knows about transformation and is ready. You are can now push modifications on launchpad. You have to set a target directory if you want to have it in a different place of
				the default one. In order to carry out the push, go on command line and write: push lp ~ username (the name you have before the @ in your mail) /collatex/florence2010 (ex.: host-003:collatex
				andreascotti$ bzr push lp:~ndrscotti/collatex/florence2010). The first time you are using the SSH-Key you will have the following answer:</p>

			<p>
				Once your key is known you wont need to confirm the connection as in this example.
			</p>

			<p>Go back on the launchpad web page and check the results of the push. Your branch should appear in the list of your contributions as well as in the list of the home page of collateX.</p>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>
